[{"answer": " So, Jennifer.  Are you ready for college next year", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I think so.  Im getting excited about going.  Ive decided that Im going t", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " So, Jennifer.  Are you ready for college next year", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Thats great!  Youve always liked science", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I think so.  Im getting excited about going.  Ive decided that Im going t", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Yeah, I think its a good choice for me.  The only thing I still have to decide o", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Thats great!  Youve always liked science", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Are you going to live on campus in the dorms", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Yeah, I think its a good choice for me.  The only thing I still have to decide o", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": "I dont know.  Im not sure if I should do that or live off-campus", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Are you going to live on campus in the dorms", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, both options probably have their benefits and downsides", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 25, "question": "I dont know.  Im not sure if I should do that or live off-campus", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Right.  Lots of people have told me that the dorms are great for new students", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Well, both options probably have their benefits and downsides", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Thats true.  Dont forget that theyre safe too, and you dont have to worr", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Right.  Lots of people have told me that the dorms are great for new students", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I didnt even think about the utilities.  Thats a good point.  But, if I lived in th", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Thats true.  Dont forget that theyre safe too, and you dont have to worr", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Those are definitely drawbacks to consider.  Well, what are your othe", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " I didnt even think about the utilities.  Thats a good point.  But, if I lived in th", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " There are a few off-campus housing options.  One is a studio apartment", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Those are definitely drawbacks to consider.  Well, what are your othe", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Theyre small though, right", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 50, "question": " There are a few off-campus housing options.  One is a studio apartment", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Yeah.  Its just a single room with a little kitchen", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Theyre small though, right", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " You might want a little more space than that.  What about your ow", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Yeah.  Its just a single room with a little kitchen", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Its too expensive for me to have my own apartment.  I was thinking abou", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " You might want a little more space than that.  What about your ow", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Are there a lot of those available", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Its too expensive for me to have my own apartment.  I was thinking abou", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Some.  Not as many as apartments.  But it would be nice.  Id have my ow", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Are there a lot of those available", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " A house might be a lot quieter than an apartment, too", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Some.  Not as many as apartments.  But it would be nice.  Id have my ow", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I think it would be.  I might feel a little lonely though, living by myself.  That", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 66, "question": " A house might be a lot quieter than an apartment, too", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Thats what I did in college", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " I think it would be.  I might feel a little lonely though, living by myself.  That", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Did you like it", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Thats what I did in college", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Oh, sure.  I loved it!  My roommates were really nice, and I always ha", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Did you like it", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Oh, sure.  I loved it!  My roommates were really nice, and I always ha", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " I mean you have to find good roommates.  Are you going to share a", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 78, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " No, I dont know anyone going to my college.  I was just going to look for ad", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 85, "question": " I mean you have to find good roommates.  Are you going to share a", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Well, some can be a nightmare.  They might be really messy, really noisy", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 89, "question": " No, I dont know anyone going to my college.  I was just going to look for ad", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " I guess Id have to be really careful who I chose", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Well, some can be a nightmare.  They might be really messy, really noisy", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " As long as you took the time to find a good roommate, it should be fine", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 94, "question": " I guess Id have to be really careful who I chose", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Right now, Im just not sure what to do", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 95, "question": " As long as you took the time to find a good roommate, it should be fine", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Well, youve got time.  Why dont you think about it some more, and mayb", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Right now, Im just not sure what to do", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " I think Ill do that.  Thats a good idea", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Well, youve got time.  Why dont you think about it some more, and mayb", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Its going to be an exciting year.  I remember when I was starting college", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 101, "question": " I think Ill do that.  Thats a good idea", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " You can come visit anytime, Aunt Mary", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 105, "question": " Its going to be an exciting year.  I remember when I was starting college", "qSentId": 104},{"answer": " You know I will", "docId": "05-09", "aSentId": 106, "question": " You can come visit anytime, Aunt Mary", "qSentId": 105}]
